哇 这是真是舒服
Oh, that feels so good.
哎呀 我运气真好 有咖啡喝还可以看现场性爱演出
Oh, lucky me. Coffee and a live sex show.
- 不好意思 什么？ - 不好意思
- I'm sorry, what?     - I'm sorry.
- 没事 我只是在念书给艾玛听   - 《柯梦波丹》吗？
- Nothing. I was just reading to Emma.     - From Cosmo?
是啊 是啊 是…
Yeah. Yeah, it's, uh:
"让你有更细致的肌肤"
"Climax Your Way to Better Skin."
我今天必须要去买衣服 这真是我最不喜欢做的事
So I have to go shopping today, which is my least favorite thing.
我实在是很不会挑选衣服
I'm so bad at picking out clothes.
所以你需要有很了解时尚的人来给你建议
So you need someone who knows fashion to, uh, tell you what looks good.
不要是我 不要是我 不要是我
Not me. Not me. Not me.
- 嘿 瑞秋？ - 怎样？
- Oh, hey, Rach?     - Yeah?
- 或许你可以带查莉去买衣服   - 喔 嗯…
- Maybe you could take Charlie shopping?     - Oh, well...
- 你可能很忙没空吧   - 你在开玩笑吗？
- I'm sure you have better things to do.     - You kidding?
瑞秋爱死逛街了 而且她品味极佳
Rachel loves to shop, and she has great taste.
就是她教我在劳动节之后不要穿白色衣服
She's the one that taught me not to wear white after Labor Day...
而且永远 永远记住在试穿衣服时 一定要穿内衣裤
and to always, always, always put on underwear when trying on clothes.
如果你有空 我会很感激你的帮忙的
If you have the time, I'd really appreciate the help.
好的 好啊 我们逛街去
Okay. Yeah, let's shop.
好的 你一定会 买回很多有格调的衣服
Okay, you are gonna come back with some very classy clothes. Ha-ha-ha.
还有一些淫荡的内衣 淫荡喔
And some slutty lingerie. Slutty!
好的 太好了 拜拜
Okay, great. All right, bye.
超级讨厌的
Pain in the ass!
- 已经挂掉了 对吗？ - 怎么了？菲比
- That's off, right?     - What's the matter, Pheebs?
麦克的姐姐刚邀请我去今晚的派对 而且他也会去
Ugh, Mike's sister just invited me to a party tonight and he's gonna be there.
她说 "别担心 我问过他了 他完全不介意见到你"
She was like, "Don't worry. I asked him and he's totally okay with seeing you."
所以现在我一定得去了 否则他会认为我很介意见到他
So now I have to go so he'll think that I'm totally okay with seeing him.
- 你根本就很介意 你还没有忘记他   - 没错
- You're not. You're hung up on him.     - Exactly.
你想要他懊悔不已 所以你一定要看起来艳光四射
You want him to eat his heart out, so you have to look fabulous.
我根本没有那样想过
I didn't even think about that.
性欲权术
Ugh. Sexual politics!
嘿 菲比 我要带查莉去逛街
Pheebs, I'm taking Charlie shopping.
- 何不一起来 我可以帮你挑衣服   - 太棒了
- Come and I'll help you find something.     - That'd be great.
真是太好了 你们三个人 一起试穿淫荡内衣
Oh, isn't that nice? The three of you, trying on slutty lingerie together.
- 我们没有要那样做   - 你为何要破坏？我得罪谁了？
- That's not what we're gonna do.     - Why'd you ruin it? Who was I hurting?
哇 还好她长得很美
Wow. Fortunately, she has a very pretty face.
我还是无法相信 我的子宫是不适应床的环境？
I still can't believe this. My uterus is an inhospitable environment?
我一直都很努力想要当个称职的女主人
I've always tried so hard to be a good hostess.
我不敢相信我的精子的活动力太低
I can't believe my sperm have low motility.
当我在长大的时候 它们倒是等不及要到处去游玩
While I was growing up, they sure seemed to be in a hurry to get places.
- 嗨   - 嗨
- Hi there.     - Hi.
关于你们上星期的测试 我很抱歉 没有什么更好的消息
I'm sorry there wasn't better news from your tests last week...
但是我想要跟你们谈谈你们可有的选择
but I wanted to talk to you about your options.
好的
Okay.
虽然你们以正常方式 受孕的机率很低…
Even though your chances of conceiving through natural means aren't great...
但是很难定论的 所以你们还是持续进行性生活
you never know, so keep having sex on a regular basis.
哎 是喔
Oh, damn it!
别担心 过一阵子你们就会习惯了
Don't worry. After a while, you'll tune it out.
在这种情况之下 最佳的选择就是…
Given your situation, the options with the greatest chances for success...
代理孕母或是经由捐赠精子受孕
would be surrogacy or insemination using a sperm donor.
好的
Okay.
如果你们认为上述两种选择都不适合 你们还是可以选择领养
If you feel that neither of those is right for you, you could always adopt.
这是个暗示吗？
Is that a hint?
我们是挺热爱你的 唐纳利医生 但是我们不想要收养你
Because we love you, Dr. Connelly, but we don't want you to be our child.
糟糕 说的话还真不受欢迎
Wow. Talk about an inhospitable environment.
嗨 你准备好要去接菲比逛街了吗？
Hi. Okay, you ready to go pick up Phoebe and go shopping?
- 我们走吧   - 好的 祝你们逛的愉快
- Let's do it.     - All right, have a good time.
那里面是找不到衣服的
Not gonna find any clothes in there.
- 你们好   - 嗨
- Hey, you guys.     - Hi.
猜猜看谁是 全国古生物学大会的主讲人？
Guess who's up for keynote speaker at the National Paleontology Conference?
- 克里斯培利吗？ - 对啊 是啊
- Uh, Chris Bailey?     - Yeah, right.
他上次准时提交摘要是什么时候呢？
When was the last time he made a submission deadline for an abstract?
你为什么要笑呢？
Why are you laughing?
只是想了解一下 当古生物学家是怎样的
Just seeing what it'd be like to be a paleontologist.
真好玩 是啊
It's fun. Yeah.
- 所以你要当主讲人？ - 是的
- You're up for keynote speaker?     - Yeah.
- 是谁做的决定呢？ - 薛曼教授
- Who's deciding?     - Professor Sherman.
- 我今天要跟他见面   - 他是个蛮难伺候的人
- I'm meeting with him today.     - He's a pretty tough guy to impress.
我想我知道要怎么迷惑他
I think I know how to dazzle him.
你应该不是要变魔术吧？
Oh, you're not gonna to do a magic trick, are you?
不是
No.
- 大家好   - 我想要问你们一个问题
- Hey, guys.     - I want to ask you something.
我可能会在这个古生物学大会演说
I may get to speak at this paleontology convention.
如果是这样 我想邀请你们来听我的演讲
If I do, I'd love for you guys to come and hear me.
我想如果说我们都有家庭 工作或是身体不适等理由是没错的
I think I can safely say that we all have family issues, work and or are sick.
- 是在巴贝多   - 但是你是最重要的
- It's in Barbados.     - But you come first.
我去定了
I'm there.
- 待会见   - 好的 拜
- We'll see you guys.     - Bye.
- 再见   - 嘿
- See you.     - Hey.
- 好 验孕诊所怎么说？ - 不像上次一样好玩
- So how did it go at the fertility clinic?     - Not as much fun as last time.
很明显地 他们只有在采精子样本时 才会给你看色情书刊
Apparently, you only get porn if you're giving a sperm sample.
那医生怎么说呢？
So, uh, what did the doctor say?
可以用代理孕母 但摩妮卡这一辈子 都在梦想怀孕…
There's surrogacy, but Monica's dreamt her whole life of carrying a child...
而她会觉得看着代理孕母怀孕 对她而言会太难受了
and she just felt that watching a surrogate would be too hard for her.
- 所以你们不考虑代理孕母？ - 没错
- So you're ruling out surrogacy?     - Yeah.
所以我不用知道那是什么意思罗？
So I don't have to learn what that means?
除了领养外 剩下的选择 就是接受精子捐赠
Aside from adoption, the only other choice is insemination...
所以我们现在在讨论精子捐赠者的事
so we're talking about sperm donors.
够了 我随时为你效劳 兄弟 她在哪？楼上吗？
Enough said. I'm there for you, man. Where is she, upstairs?
那你的感觉呢？
How do you feel about all this?
我真希望我们有更简单的方式可生孩子 但是我们别无选择
I wish there was an easier way for us to have a child, but there isn't one.
别这样 罗斯 做做好人 挺身而出吧
Come on, Ross, be a good guy. Step up and do it.
什么？
What?
什么？不 我不会把班给他们的
What? No! I'm not gonna give them Ben!
我们从磁共振造影跟脱氧核醣核酸测试里取得的数据…
The data we're receiving from MRI scans and DNA testing...
资料是很惊人的
of these fossils are staggering.
嗯
Mm-hm.
我的意思是 我们一直以来都将李奇年代法视为理所当然
I mean, we've been accepting Leakey's dates as a given.
但是如果它的误差 即使只有十万年左右…
But if they're off by even a 100,000 years or so...
那你可以舍弃我们大部分推论…
then you can just throw most of our assumptions...
你知道的 丢到垃圾桶里
you know, right in the trash.
所以 我要说的是…
So, what I'm saying is...
是那…
Is that...
是所受影响的后果是很大的
Is that, uh, repercussions could be huge.
我是说 不只是在古生物学 但是如果你仔细想想…
I mean, not just in paleontology, but if you think about it...
甚至是在进化生物学 基因学 地质学
in evolutionary biology, uh genetics, uh, geology.
我是说 真的 无限想象的空间
I mean, truly, the mind boggles.
嗯 结果不该是这样的
Well, that's not what you want.
- 男人的动机？ - 我要喷一点
- Incentive for Men?     - I'll take some of that.
- 菲比 那是男生的香水   - 我知道
- That's for men.     - I know.
在我等一下去派对时…
When I go to the party later...
麦克会知道我已经忘了他 因为我闻起来会有另一个男人的味道
Mike will know I'm over him because I'll smell like another guy.
来吧
Yeah.
好了
Okay.
太好了 我在跟俄罗斯计程车司机约会
Oh, good, I'm dating a Russian cabdriver.
拜托 有人买这个吗？这闻起来像是甜菜
Seriously, does anyone buy this? I smell like beets.
我真的很喜欢那些有垫肩的外套 在哪边有呢？
I really like those jackets with the shoulder pads in them. Where are those?
梅兰妮葛丽芬在《上班女郎》里面穿的
Um, on Melanie Griffith in Working Girl.
我想适合你穿的在这边
Um, I think what you want is over here.
我就知道 我需要有人帮我
See, I told you I needed someone.
对了 为了要谢谢你 我真的很想请你吃饭
By the way, as a thank you, I would really love to take you out.
- 真的吗？ - 对 乔伊跟我今晚要去看电影
- Really?     - Joey and I are going to a movie tonight.
- 你想要一起去吗？ - 我不行
- You want to come?     - Oh, I can't.
因为我看过了
Because I've seen them.
你已经看过所有的电影了？
You've seen all the movies?
是啊 我为之入迷
Yeah. I'm a big fan.
电影迷
Of the movies.
所有的电影
You know, motion pictures.
包括老电影
The talkies.
瑞秋 你可以跟我进去试衣间试穿吗？
Rach, will you come with me to a dressing room?
- 当然   - 好的
- Sure.     - Okay.
或许我们可以做别的事
Maybe we could do something else.
你知道的 那要看是什么事 很多东西我都做过了
You know, that depends on what it is. I've done a lot of stuff.
你刚刚是怎么了？ 你不喜欢查莉吗？
So, what were you doing out there? Do you not like Charlie?
她还好啦 我不知道 我只是跟她不投缘吧
She's okay. I don't know, I just don't get a really good vibe from her.
- 为什么？ - 我不知道
- Why?     - I don't know.
你知道的 只是她的一举一动 聪明的要命…
You know, just the way she waltzed in here all smart...
而且又高挑 你知道的…
and tall, you know...
然后又把乔伊迷的东倒西歪的 别人都没有机会
and just swept Joey off his feet. Nobody else has a chance.
还有谁呢？
Who else?
任何人啊
Anybody.
你
You.
我
Me.
你知道的 摩妮卡的妈
You know, Monica's mom.
- 你喜欢乔伊？ - 菲比
- You like Joey?     - Shh! Phoebe!
好吧 你说的没错 我对他是有点感觉 只是…
All right, look, I do. I have a little thing for him. Just...
- 喔 我的天啊   - 是肉欲的
- Oh, my God.     - It's just physical.
我已经完全控制住了 好吗？只是当我看到他们在一起…
I have it totally under control, okay? It's just when I see them together...
有时候 我就会有点嫉妒
sometimes, I just get a little jealous.
哇 好讽刺喔 他以前喜欢你过 然后现在你喜欢…
Wow. Isn't that ironic that he liked you, and now you like...?
我知道啦
I get it!
好吧 一切都控制住就好了
All right, as long as it's under control.
你不可以采取任何行动 他已经跟她在一起了
You can't do anything about it. He's already dating her.
她是个好人 那样是不对的
She is a nice person. That wouldn't be right.
我知道 我知道 所以没事啦
I know, I know. So it's just not a big deal.
- 你可以不要说出去吗？ - 当然
- So can we keep this between us?     - Sure.
太好了 因为我得出去了 我快被甜菜味熏死了
Great, because I gotta get out of here. The smell of beets is killing me.
- 查莉可能会有耳聋的双胞胎妹妹吗？ - 嗯
- Any chance Charlie has a deaf twin?     - Mm.
- 嗨 亲爱的   - 嘿
- Hi, honey.     - Hey.
我带个朋友回来吃晚餐 这是我同事柴克
I brought a friend home for dinner. This is Zack from work.
当然啦 很高兴再见到你 柴克
Oh, of course. It's so nice to see you again, Zack.
- 我也是   - 你们并没有见过面
- You too.     - You guys haven't actually met before.
天啊 你们还真有礼貌
But, boy, you're both polite.
请坐 我帮你拿啤酒
Have a seat. I'll get you a beer.
- 我来拿   - 谢谢
- I got it.     - Thanks.
- 柴克不错吧？ - 是啊 应该吧
- So Zack's pretty nice, huh?     - Yeah, I guess.
那你想不想和他生个小孩呢？
So how would you like to have a baby that's half yours and half his?
什么？
Excuse me?
我们在讲的是精子捐赠者 而柴克或许就是适当的人选
We're talking about sperm donors, and Zack may be the guy.
他很聪明 健康 体格强壮 我是说 他是最佳人选了
Look. He's intelligent, he's healthy, he's athletic. I mean, he's sperm-tastic!
钱德 这太疯狂了 你是怎么跟他说的？
Chandler, this is crazy. Well, what did you even say to him?
"上来看看我老婆 给我们你的精子"
"Come up. Meet my wife. Give us your sperm."
不是 我邀请他来吃晚餐让你见见他
I invited him to dinner so you'd get a chance to get to know him.
如果去精子银行 我们根本不能见到那个捐赠者
With a sperm bank, you never meet the guy, get to check him out.
- 钱德   - 我告诉你 他棒透了
- Chandler!     - I'm telling you, he's great.
我是说 即使我的精子没有问题 我也认为我们应该选择他
I mean, even if my sperm worked fine, I think he'd be the way to go.
我不要淌这浑水
I'm not going to be a part of this.
你不能随便带个男的回来 就当精子捐赠者
You can't bring some random guy home and expect him to be our sperm donor.
好吧
Okay.
- 柴克？ - 谢谢
- Zack?     - Thanks.
你有杯垫吗？我不想留下杯印
Do you have a coaster? I don't want to make a ring.
多聊聊你自己 柴克
Tell me about yourself, Zack.
天啊 你觉得她听到了吗？如果她听到就惨了
Oh, God, do you think she heard? It'd be so bad if she heard.
或许她没有听到 我到隔壁间说话 你待在这里
Maybe she didn't hear. I'll go into that dressing room and talk. You stay here.
- 看看你是不是可以听到我说话   - 好的
- See if you can hear me.     - Okay, great.
喔 感谢上帝 我听不到你说话
Oh, thank God, I can't hear a word that you're saying.
- 我还没有开始说话   - 那回去里面然后说话啊
- I didn't say anything yet.     - Well, get back in there and talk.
我是瑞秋
I'm Rachel.
让艾玛在电话上跟我朋友讲话 真的很讨厌
It's so annoying when I put Emma on the phone to talk with my friends.
什么？
What?
嗯 有些事是很难当你的面说的
Well, some things are just hard to say to your face.
好吧 我听到了 表示她也听到了
Okay, well, I heard that. Which means that she heard it too.
- 我们有麻烦了   - 喔 我们该怎么办呢？
- We have a problem.     - Oh, what are we gonna do?
就老实跟她说吧
Just be honest with her.
喔 我的天啊
Oh, my God!
父母让婴儿听电话 的确是很讨厌
It is annoying when parents put babies on the phone.
好了 你说够了
All right, enough out of you!
- 喂？ - 乔伊 我要跟查莉讲话 她在吗？
- Hello?     - I need to talk to Charlie. Is she there?
不在 她跟瑞秋去逛街了 为什么？怎么了？
No, she, uh, went shopping with Rachel. Why? What's up?
我正在跟薛曼教授 讨论关于我当主讲人的事
I'm meeting with Professor Sherman about my being the keynote speaker.
- 进行的如何呢？ - 可以更顺利的
- How's it going?     - It could be better.
他… 他睡着了
He, um... He fell asleep.
什么？但是我已经 订了到百慕达的机票了
What? But I already bought my ticket to Bermuda!
- 是巴贝多   - 好啦 我再租车开过去
- Barbados.     - Fine, I'll rent a car and drive.
罗斯 你一定要得到这工作
You have to get that job.
我应该怎么办呢？他完全睡着了
What am I supposed to do? He's out cold.
事实上 刚刚他还在说梦话
In fact, he was just talking in his sleep before...
而且他还要一个叫法兰的人 "再打用力点"
and evidently he wants someone named Fran to "spank him harder."
- 那叫醒他吧   - 我不行
- Well, just wake him up.     - I can't.
如果他发现我是让他睡着的人 我就得不到这个工作了
If he realizes that I'm the one who put him to sleep, I won't get the job.
那倒是挺难的
Ooh, that's a tough one.
等等 这以前也发生在我身上过
Oh, wait a minute. This happened to me before.
是啊 我之前在试演一出戏剧的时候 那个制片睡着了 我…
Yeah, I was auditioning for a play, and the producer fell asleep. I...
不 等等
No, wait a minute.
其实是我睡着了
It was me who fell asleep.
拜托 莎士比亚 来点动作场面吧？
I mean, hey, Shakespeare, how about a chase scene once in a while?
- 嘿 晚餐好了   - 我先去洗手
- Hey, guys, dinner's ready.     - I'm gonna go wash up first.
谢了
Thanks.
你觉得呢？我要我的孩子有他的基因 那双眼睛 那颧骨
What do you think? I want his genes for my kid. Those eyes, those cheekbones.
好了 可能是过度狂热 也有可能是同志
Okay, there's enthusiastic, and there's just plain gay.
- 你不喜欢他   - 我想他不错
- You don't like him.     - I think he's fine.
但是我们对他了解不够
But we don't know anything real about him.
- 我希望我们可知道多一点   - 好的 跟着我的话锋转
- I wish we could get more information.     - All right, just follow my lead.
- 你们家真是好棒   - 谢谢 我很喜欢这地方
- You guys have a great place here.     - Thanks. I'm crazy about our place.
嘿 说到疯狂…
Hey, speaking of crazy...
你们家有遗传性精神疾病吗？
do you have a history of mental illness in the family?
没有 但是我是有个叔叔投票给杜凯吉斯
Uh, no. Although, I did have an uncle who voted for Dukakis.
那真的不是我们想知道的
That's really not the kind of thing we're looking for.
好的
Okay.
告诉我 你们是怎么认识的呢？
So, um, tell me, how'd you guys meet?
刚开始是朋友 在伦敦喝醉 你知道的
Oh, friends first, drunk in London, you know the story.
我有个更棒的问题要问你
I've got a better question for you:
你或是你的近亲 有人有糖尿病吗？
Do you or any of your blood relatives have diabetes?
没有
No.
心脏病？阿兹海默症？痛风？
Uh, heart disease? Alzheimer's? Gout?
你们不常请朋友到家里用餐 是吗？
You guys don't have people for dinner a lot, huh?
我们只是在找话题聊聊
We're just making conversation.
好吧 我今天听到一个笑话 真的是挺好笑的
Yeah, well, okay. I heard a joke today. It's pretty funny.
你知道有什么是不好笑的吗？雄性秃头
You know what's not funny? Male pattern baldness.
你们今晚对我很有兴趣 我很受宠若惊
You guys have shown a lot of interest in me tonight, and I'm flattered...
而且老实说 是有点受惊
and quite frankly, a little frightened.
我们可以聊聊别的话题吗？
Can we just talk about something else?
- 当然   - 好的
- Sure.      - All right.
这个意大利水饺真是美味
This ravioli's delicious.
我发现你享用那水饺的牙齿真是整齐
I notice you're enjoying that ravioli with a beautiful set of teeth.
你小时候有戴牙套吗？
Did you have braces as a child?
- 不 没有   - 太好了
- No, I didn't.     - Yes!
我们很重视牙齿的 柴克
We're teeth people, Zack.
我们直接过去问她有没有听到
Let's just do it. Let's just go over there and see if she heard.
- 好主意   - 好的
- Good plan.     - Okay.
- 什么？你是在做什么呢？ - 对不起 瑞秋
- What? Where are you going?     - Oh, I'm sorry, Rachel.
我没有时问玩你的幼稚游戏 好吗？
I don't have time for your childish games, okay?
我还得去找很惊艳的衣服穿
I still have to find something incredible to wear...
那我才可以在"谁先忘了谁"上 打败麦克
so I can beat Mike at "Who's More Over Who"!
- 你好   - 你好
- Hey. Hi.     - Hey.
- 你去哪里了？ - 去试穿衣服
- Where have you been?     - Trying on clothes.
真的吗？在试衣间吗？喔 真奇怪
Oh, really? In the dressing room? Well, that's so weird.
菲比跟我刚刚也在试衣间 天啊 这世界真是小
Phoebe and I were in the dressing room. Gosh, it's just such a small world.
瑞秋 我听到你们俩的对谈了
Rachel, I heard you two guys whispering.
天啊 你听到了 好的 听着 让我解释
Oh, God, you did, you heard. Okay, look, let me explain.
没有必要解释 我都听到了
There's nothing to explain. I heard you.
菲比喜欢乔伊
Phoebe likes Joey.
是啊
Yeah.
我不明白 我是说菲比喜欢乔伊
I don't understand it. I mean, Phoebe likes Joey...
可是她却来买衣服 来惊艳另一个男人？
and then she's here to buy a dress to impress another guy?
是啊 菲比就是那样 她就是那样 你知道的 她就是全部都要
Yeah, that's Phoebe. That's Phoebe. You know, she just wants them all.
那就像是女色情狂
It's, like, she's nympho.
- 哇   - 是啊
- Wow!     - Yeah.
对了 我有听到你告诉她 不可以做任何事
You know, by the way, I heard you tell her not to do anything.
谢谢你替我说话 天啊 你真是个好人
Thanks for sticking up for me. God, you are such a nice person.
我尽量
I try.
哦
Oh!
我的天啊 你真的要我当主讲人吗？
Oh, my God, you really want me to be the keynote speaker?
谢谢你
Thank you!
不用客气
You're welcome.
哇 你看起来…
Wow! You look...
真是辣得让人不想吃东西
stop-eating hot!
这是最高阶级的辣耶
Which is like the highest level of hotness.
你确定吗？因为我真的很不想去这派对
Okay, are you sure? Because I am really dreading going to this party.
那就别去啊
Then don't go.
麦克知道我要去 如果我没出现 他会以为那是因为他…
Mike knows I'm coming. If I don't show up, he'll think it's because of him...
我那样就会很没面子 这对我来说是很严重的事
and then I'm gonna lose face. That's a very serious thing in my culture.
好吧 那就去派对吧 然后假装已经完全不受麦克影响
All right, then you go to that party, and you pretend to be over Mike.
之后你再来我家 我再帮你好好借酒解愁
Afterward, you come to my place and I'll get you good and drunk.
没问题 好的
You got it. Okay.
但是不要喝你自己酿的酒好吗？
But not on the wine that you made, okay?
因为我不想要再进急诊室了
Because I just don't want to go back to the emergency room.
大卫？
David?
菲比
Phoebe! Hi.
- 喔 我的天   - 嗨
- Oh my god     - Hi.
哇 你看起来真是漂亮极了
Wow! You look unbelievable.
喔 是啊 嗯…
Oh, yeah, well...
你在这里做什么呢？
What are you doing here?
我从明斯克回来了 永久
Well, I'm back from Minsk. Uh, permanently.
发生什么事呢？
Well, what happened?
记得我正在尝试制造…
Remember how I was trying to achieve...
次原子阳电子净化吗？
the positronic distillation of subatomic particles?
是啊
Yeah.
在经过八年的研究之后 我发现…
Well, after eight years of research, I discovered...
那是做不到的
that it can't be done.
嗯…
Well...
你终于回来了真是好 你好吗？
great that you're back. How are you?
- 很好 过的还不错   - 很好
- Good. Good. Life is good.     - Good.
- 我现在有交往的对象了   - 噢
- Well, I'm seeing someone.     - Oh.
- 这样啊 恭喜你了   - 是啊
- Good for you.     - Yeah.
她也是科学家 很聪明也很漂亮
She's also a scientist, so she's very smart and pretty and, um...
而且事实上是因为你 我们才在一起的
It's actually because of you that we're together.
我是说 我看到你跟那个麦克在一起
I mean, I saw what you had with that Mike guy...
然后我告诉自己 "天啊 我也想要那样"
and I just said, "Boy, I want that."
- 麦克跟我分手了   - 你在开玩笑吧
- Mike and I broke up.     - You're kidding me.
因为我没有在跟谁交往 完全是我编出来的
Because I'm not seeing anybody. I just totally made that up.
- 真的吗？ - 我不知道为什么 我很抱歉
- Really?     - I don't know why, I'm sorry.
我猜我只是不想没面子
I guess I just didn't want to lose face.
我能了解
I understand.
是啊 好的 那…
Yeah. Okay. So then, okay...
我们都住在纽约 没有交往对象
So we're both living in New York, not seeing anyone.
- 这太不像我们了   - 是啊 我知道
- That's so not like us.     - Yeah, I know.
嗯 这或许是个蠢问题 看到你穿成这样…
Well, this is probably a stupid question, seeing that you look like that...
但是你现在有要去什么地方吗？
but, um, do you have someplace that you need to be right now?
嗯…
Well...
没有
No.
- 那你想不想去喝点东西呢？ - 我很想
- Well, do you want to get a drink?     - I'd love to.
- 太棒了   - 好的
- Great.     - Okay.
你有闻到甜菜味吗？
Uh, do you smell beets?
好吧 站到我的逆风边
Oh, all right, stay upwind of me.
嘿 那是菲比 那是麦克吗？
Hey, there's Phoebe. Is that Mike she's with?
不是 那是大卫
No, that's David.
还有第三个男人？
There's a third guy?
只是冰山的一角
Tip of the iceberg.
我现在要走了
I'm gonna take off now.
你们会让我回家吗？
You're gonna let me go home, aren't you?
你确定不要再多坐一下吗？
Sure you don't want to stay a little longer?
不了 我应该回家了 我有点累
No, I should get home. I'm kind of tired.
你很容易累吗？
Are you always tired?
因为这很有可能是忧郁症的前兆
Because that could be a sign of clinical depression.
不 只是要想出我祖父母是几岁过世的 这让我很累
No, it's tiring to figure out the age at which all my grandparents died.
- 明天见   - 好的
- I'll see you tomorrow.     - Okay.
再见
Bye.
我想我们找到我们的精子了
I think we found our sperm.
他看起来是挺完美的
He does seem pretty perfect.
你也这么认为吗？我要开口问他吗？
Yeah? You think so? Should I ask him?
不要
No.
为什么呢？就只因为他曾祖母有肥胖症吗？
Why not? Just because his great-grandmother was obese?
反正我们的孩子也是会从你那遗传到
Our kid's gonna get that from you anyway.
不 不是那个缘故
No, that's not it.
只是在我们问他那些问题时…
It's just that when we were asking him all those questions before...
我才意识到我不在乎他是不是世上最完美的男人
I just realized I don't care if he is the most perfect guy in the world.
- 他不是你   - 是啊 他比我更好
- He's not you.     - Yeah, he's better!
不 他不是
No, he's not.
如果我不能跟你怀孕 我也不想跟他…
If I can't get pregnant with you, then I don't want to get pregnant by him...
或是跟任何人
or anyone else.
- 真的？你确定吗？ - 是的 我确定
- Really? Are you sure?     - Yeah, I'm sure.
感谢上帝 因为我也不想这样做
Thank God, because I don't wanna do this either.
我会这样做 是因为我以为你想这样
I was just doing it because I thought that was what you wanted.
我是丈夫 我理当要提供精子的
I'm the husband. I'm supposed to bring the sperm.
这真是太贴心了
That is so sweet.
我爱你
I love you.
所以你知道我们唯一的选择就是…
So you know this leaves us with...
领养
Adoption.
你觉得如何呢？
How do you feel about that?
我想我没问题
I think I feel okay about it.
事实上我觉得非常的好
Actually, I think I feel really good about it.
我也是
Me too.
我想找到一个需要家庭温暖的小孩 然后跟你一起抚养他
I wanna find a baby that needs a home, and I wanna raise it with you.
然后我想用我们自己的方式来乱养他
And I wanna mess it up in our own specific way.
这就是决定吗？我们真的要领养？
So this is it? We're really gonna adopt?
是的
Yeah.
- 我的天 我们要当父母亲了   - 我们会是很棒的父母
- Oh, my God! We're gonna be parents!     - We are gonna be great parents.
而且可能会很快
And it could be soon.
我是说 想想看 就是现在 在外面某个地方…
I mean, think about it. Right now, somewhere out there...
我们的孩子可能正被受孕
our baby could be being conceived.
等等 如果我们够幸运 而且我们真的 真的 真的很安静…
Wait. If we're lucky, and we're really, really, really quiet...
我们或许可以听到保险套破裂的声音
we may be able to hear the sound of a condom breaking.
嘿 柴克
Hey, Zack.
嘿 钱德
Hey, Chandler.
我想为昨晚的事道歉
I wanted to apologize for last night.
我感到我们让你很不舒服
I got the feeling we made you uncomfortable.
- 不 并没有   - 真的吗？
- No, you didn't.     - Really?
没错 你们是有
No, you did.
我老婆跟我越界了
My wife and I have some boundary issues.
有时候我们会问些很不适当的问题
Sometimes we ask inappropriate questions.
我们正在改进中
We're working on it.
- 这些是星期五推销会的看板   - 谢谢
- Here are the boards for Friday's pitch.     - Thank you.
你知不知道珍娜是否要留着她的孩子？
You wouldn't know if she's planning on keeping her baby, would you?